Preliminary Guide to the Interdisciplinary Studies Records, 1998 - 2006
Duke University. University Archives
Interdisciplinary Studies records 1998-2006
Duke University. University Archives
Duke University. Interdisciplinary Studies.
31.5 linear feet Extent: 23,000 Items
Duke University's strategic plan emphasizes interdisciplinary studies because important teaching, learning, and research often occur across the traditional boundaries of disciplines, departments, or schools. Interdisciplinary Studies at Duke University became an office under the direction of the Provost with the appointment of the first Vice Provost for Interdisciplinary Studies in 1998. Prior to this, direction of interdisciplinary studies was a responsibility of the Dean of the Graduate School/Vice Provost for Graduate Education. Records contain subject files, correspondence, reports, and planning documents related to Interdisciplinary Studies at Duke, including the Franklin Center for Interdisciplinary and International Studies, the Franklin Humanities Institute, Information Science and Information Studies, Women's Studies, Science Technology and Human Values, the Black Faculty Initiative, the University Scholars Program, global health, arts and humanities, the arts warehouse, development and grants, and faculty involvement with interdisciplinary teaching.
UA.07.07.0001
Language: Material in English
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
For a period of twenty-five years from the origin of the material, permission in writing from the office of origin and the University Archivist is required for use. After twenty-five years, records that have been processed may be consulted with the permission of the University Archivist.
Records, such as search committee files or others pertaining to employment where individuals are identified, are closed for 70 years.
Records of the University's Board of Trustees which have been existence for at least fifty years are available for scholarly research with the permission of the University Archivist. Access to records which have been in existence for less than fifty years shall be granted only by special permission, in writing, from the Board of Trustees.
Unprocessed materials are closed pending processing.
In off-site storage; 48 hours advance notice is required for use.
Provenance
The Interdisciplinary Studies Records were received by the University Archives as a transfer in 2005-2006.
In September 2007 box 16 was added to UA2006-0036. This box was originally slated to be transferred with the 2006 Accession, but was overlooked at the time.
Accession UA2009-0037 was transferred to the Archives in August 2009.
Historical Note
Duke University's strategic plan emphasizes interdisciplinary studies because important teaching, learning, and research often occur across the traditional boundaries of disciplines, departments, or schools. Interdisciplinary Studies at Duke University became an office under the direction of the Provost with the appointment of Cathy Davidson as the first Vice Provost for Interdisciplinary Studies in 1998. Prior to this, direction of interdisciplinary studies was a responsibility of the Dean of the Graduate School/Vice Provost for Graduate Education.
Collection Overview
Records contain subject files, correspondence, reports, and planning documents related to Interdisciplinary Studies at Duke, including the Franklin Center for Interdisciplinary and International Studies, the Franklin Humanities Institute, Information Science and Information Studies, Women's Studies, Science Technology and Human Values, the Black Faculty Initiative, the University Scholars Program, global health, arts and humanities, the arts warehouse, development and grants, and faculty involvement with interdisciplinary teaching.
Subject Headings
Duke University -- Curricula; Duke University. Interdisciplinary Studies; Duke University -- History
Preliminary Description of the Collection
- 2005 Transfer [UA2005-0012]
  - Franklin Center opening celebration (Box 1)
  - Hanes Annex, Trent Hall (Box 1)
  - Franklin Center technology (Box 1)
  - Franklin Institute (Box 1)
  - Franklin Seminars (Box 1)
  - Franklin Fellows (Box 1)
  - Humanities Initiative (Box 1)
  - Genome Sciences and Policy (Box 2)
  - Institute for Human Genetics (Box 2)
  - Cross Genealogies Correspondence (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous E-mails (Box 2)
  - Cross Genealogies (Box 2)
  - Subsidy for Global Institute (Box 2)
  - Graduate School: Joint Ph. D. (Box 2)
  - Graduate School: Mentoring (Box 2)
  - Harvard University Boston Globe (Box 2)
  - Harvard University Sara Lightfoot Lawrence (Box 2)
  - CHPLM Kate Whetten-Goldstein (Box 2)
  - Health, Policy, Law and Management (Box 2)
  - History Department (Box 2)
    - Monica Green (Box 2)
    - Charles Payne (Box 2)
    - Alex Roland (Box 2)
  - Inner Staff (Box 2)
    - Summer Projects 1999 (Box 2)
    - Summer Projects 2000 (Box 2)
    - Clay Cristensen (Box 2)
    - 1999-2000 (Box 2)
  - Integrated Toxicology (Box 2)
  - Intellectual Property (Box 2)
  - International Affairs Committee (Box 2)
  - International Office (Box 2)
  - Internationalization (Box 2)
  - Center for International Studies (Box 2)
  - Interschool Venture Fund (Box 2)
  - Latin American Studies: Moreiras-Rockefeller (Box 2)
  - Law School (Box 2)
    - Catherine Adcock Amway (Box 2)
    - Doriane Coleman (Box 2)
    - Search Plans (Box 2)
  - Marine Lab: Richard Barber (Box 2)
  - MLK Planning (Box 2)
  - Math (Box 2)
    - Jack Bookman (Box 2)
    - Arlie Petters (Box 2)
  - Masters of Health Sciences in Clinical Leadership (Box 2)
  - Mellon Lecturing Fellows: Proposals, Drafts and Notes (Box 2)
  - Music: Cecil Taylor (Box 2)
  - Near Surface Crustal Studies (Box 2)
  - Neurobiology: Gillian Einstein (Box 2)
  - New Educational Markets (Box 2)
  - NSOE: 1998-1999 (Box 2)
  - Sciences Collaboration- North Carolina (Box 2)
  - Oceans Connect 1998-2000 (Box 2)
  - Packard Foundation (Box 2)
  - Nanoscience (Box 2)
  - Political Science: McClain, Paula (Box 2)
  - Romance Studies: Miguel Garci-Gomez (Box 2)
  - Scholarships at Duke: Krause, Robert and Kathleen (Box 2)
  - Smith Fund 2000-2001 Selection Process (Box 2)
  - South Atlantic Quarterly (Box 2)
  - Students Against Sweatshops (Box 2)
  - Town Gown 2000 (Box 2)
  - UCHRI Director Search (Box 2)
  - University Scholars Program (Box 2)
    - Financial Aid 2000-2001 (Box 2)
    - Admission and Financial Aid 10/25/99 Meeting (Box 2)
    - Finals Weekend 2000 (Box 2)
    - University Scholars 1999-2000 (Box 2)
    - University Scholars History and Background Information (Box 2)
    - Director (Box 2)
    - Financial Plan, Jim Roberts Budget Relief Graduate Program 1999-2000 Program (Box 2)
  - Women's Studies 1998-1999 Ad Hoc Review Committee Tenure Lines (Box 2)
  - Woodrow Wilson Foundation: Teachers as Scholars (Box 2)
  - Arts and Humanities Proposal Responses (Box 2)
  - Arts Management (Box 2)
  - Arts and Humanities Working Group (Box 2)
  - A & H Proposals (Box 2)
  - Krause scholarship (Box 3)
  - Smith fund (Box 3)
  - South Atlantic Quarterly (Box 3)
  - Town Gown 2000 (Box 3)
  - University Scholars Program (Box 3)
  - Women's Studies Ad Hoc Review Committee (Box 3)
  - Arts and Humanities Working Group (Box 3)
  - Black Faculty Initiative (Box 4)
    - Trachette Jackson (Box 4)
    - 1998-1999 (Box 4)
    - ISDS Postdoc (Box 4)
    - 1999-2000 report DRAFTS (Box 4)
  - SACS Self-Study (Box 4)
  - Sarah Stanbury (Box 4)
  - Verena Conley (Box 4)
  - Ten Universities: 12/9/98 Meeting (Box 4)
  - Vice Provosts Council: 1999-2000 (Box 4)
  - Duke University Annual Report 1997-1998 (Box 4)
  - Campaign for Duke prospectus (Box 4)
  - University Scholars Program (Box 4)
    - packet for new Unis, August 1999 (Box 4)
    - web page (Box 4)
    - Professional Schools (Box 4)
    - Planning (Box 4)
    - 1999 Finalists (Box 4)
    - Inquiries (Box 4)
    - Selection 1999 (Box 4)
  - Work Culture Task Force: 1997-1998 (Box 4)
  - Duke University at the Millenium: DRAFTS (Box 4)
  - 1999 Rockefeller: Drafts, Notes, Emails (Box 4)
  - 1999 Rockefeller: Backup Materials (Box 4)
  - 1999 Rockefeller: Proposal and Supporting Letters (Box 4)
  - Women's Studies (Box 5)
    - Notes for Academic Council (Box 5)
    - Press (Box 5)
    - Director (Box 5)
    - WS Faculty Responses (Box 5)
    - Notes and Correspondence (Box 5)
    - Minutes (Box 5)
    - Faculty Vitae (Box 5)
    - Other Universities (Box 5)
    - Report (Box 5)
    - Background Information (Box 5)
  - Academic Affairs (Box 6)
  - Arts and Humanities (Box 6)
  - Hayti Heritage Center (Box 6)
  - Molecular Biophysics (Box 6)
  - Women's Taskforce (Box 6)
  - Franklin Center: Other universities' humanities centers (Box 6)
  - Affirmative Action (Box 7)
  - African-American Issues (Box 7)
  - Aging & Human Development (Box 7)
  - Arts at Duke (Box 7)
  - Board of Trustees-Minutes (Box 7)
  - Correspondence-Miscellaneous (Box 7)
  - Deans Cabinet (Box 7)
  - Drama Program (Box 7)
  - Franklin Center (Box 7)
    - Renovations Plans (Box 7)
    - Signage (Box 7)
    - Parking (Box 7)
    - Renovation Plans 2001 (Box 7)
    - Community Affairs Task Force (Box 7)
    - General Correspondence (Box 7)
    - Naming BOT (Box 7)
    - Book Subsidy (Box 7)
    - Design (Box 7)
    - Higher Education in Developing Countries, Peril & Promise (Box 7)
    - Renderings (Box 7)
  - Franklin Humanities Institute (Box 7)
    - Seminars 2001-2002 (Box 7)
    - Newsletter examples (Box 7)
    - Co-Director's Lunches (Karla) (Box 7)
    - Office Procedures (Box 7)
    - Public Affairs (Box 7)
    - Meetings 2001-2002 (Box 7)
    - Abe, Bartlett, Finucci, Greer, Hill, Hillard, Jaffe, Kelly, Mclsaac, Moreno, Mottahedeh, Nathans, Nelson, Paley, Parker, Weisenfelds (Box 7)
    - Seminar Topics & Papers 2002-2003 (Box 7)
    - Seminar Rejects 2002-2003 (Box 7)
    - Paul Berliner 2002-2003 (Box 7)
    - 2002-2003 Graduate Fellowship/Library Fellowship Applications (Box 7)
  - Institute of the Arts (Box 8)
  - ISIS (Box 8)
    - Meetings (General) (Box 8)
    - STS List of Instructors (Box 8)
    - CIT Grant (Box 8)
    - Free Space (Box 8)
    - Law School (Box 8)
    - Proposal Examples (Box 8)
    - Robertson Scholars Collaborative Fund Grant (Box 8)
    - TSI Survey (Box 8)
    - Status Report 2001 (Box 8)
    - Center for Interspacial Engineering (Box 8)
    - Initiative Building on Excellence (Box 8)
    - Start Up Process (Box 8)
    - Transition (Box 8)
    - E-Learning Retreat (Box 8)
  - Inner Staff (Box 8)
  - Jenkins-Internet Policy Institute (Box 8)
  - Libraries-Perkins Library Renovation File (Box 8)
  - Recruitment & Retention of Minority Administrators Task Force (Box 8)
  - STHV (Box 8)
- 2006 Addition [UA2006-0036] (Box 8)
  - AAAS, 2003 (Box 9)
  - Hauerwas, Stanley: AAAS, 2001 (Box 9)
  - Kaplan, Alice: AAAS, 2002 (Box 9)
  - AAU, 2002-2004 (Box 9)
  - Vaughn, John: AAU, 2002-2004 (Box 9)
  - AAUP (Vancouver, BC), 2004 (Box 9)
  - Abe, Stan: Franklin Institute workshop/seminar, "Theory and Premodern Scholarship", 2002 (Box 9)
  - ASP, 2006 (Box 9)
  - American Literature, 2004 (Box 9)
  - American Studies, 2002 (Box 9)
  - Amistad, 2002 (Box 9)
  - AIPs planning: Arts and humanitites, 2000 (Box 9)
  - Arts, Cultures, and Technologies complex: Arts and humanities, 2001 (Box 9)
  - Arts and humanities working groups, 2001 (Box 9)
  - Arts Warehouse, 2003-2005 (Box 9)
  - Boyle, Jamie, 2003 (Box 9)
  - Brav, Alon, 2004 (Box 9)
  - Brodhead, Richard: report committee, 2002-2004 (Box 9)
  - Campt, Tina, 2005-2006 (Box 9)
  - Carnegie Foundation, 2003 (Box 9)
  - Centers, 2004 (Box 9)
  - Child and Health Policy Initiative, 2006 (Box 9)
  - Center for Global Studies in Humanities, 2006 (Box 9)
  - Center for Integrated Education, Research, and Development, 2005 (Box 9)
  - Certificate program, 2002 (Box 9)
  - Creative technology at Duke, 2003 (Box 9)
  - Cross university teaching, 2004 (Box 9)
  - Cultural anthropology: Gupta and Mankekar, 2000 (Box 9)
  - Cultural anthropology: Wendy Lutrell, 1998 (Box 9)
  - Cultural anthropology: Orin Starn (Box 9)
  - Dees, Greg: Fuqua School of Business, 2003 (Box 9)
  - Development (12 folders), 1999-2004 (Box 9)
  - Dissertation, 2005 (Box 9)
  - Digital Promise (3 folders), 2005 (Box 9)
  - Dorfman, Ariel, 2003 (Box 9)
  - Duke Performances, 2004 (Box 9)
  - Duke University Museum of Art, 2005-2006 (Box 9)
  - Duke Population Research Institute, 2005 (Box 9)
  - Durham Library Humanities Committee, 2004 (Box 9)
  - Engaging Humanites, 2003 (Box 9)
  - English dept. review, 2004 (Box 9)
  - Evaluations, 2004 (Box 9)
  - Feller, Irwin, 2004 (Box 9)
  - Film and Video Program, 2003 (Box 9)
  - Ford Foundation, 2002 (Box 9)
  - Franklin Center budget meeting (Box 10)
  - Center for Nonlinear Complex Systems (Box 10)
  - Sawyer Seminar proposals (Box 10)
  - French and Francophone Studies (Box 10)
  - Analysis of trends and cumulative funding data (Box 10)
  - Center for Health Policy, Law, and Management, 2004-2005 (Box 11)
  - French and Francophone Studies, 2005 (Box 11)
  - Fulbright Scholar: Yu, Jianhua, 2002-2003 (Box 11)
  - Full Frame Documentary Film Festival, 2003-2005 (Box 11)
  - Garci-Gomez, Miguel, 2004 (Box 11)
  - Gates Millennium Scholars, 2000 (Box 11)
  - Pre-Modern German Studies, Center for, 2001 (Box 11)
  - Global Health, 2004-2005 (Box 11)
  - Global Studies in the Humanities, 2003-2004 (Box 11)
  - Glymph, Thavolia: Race, Space, Place project, 2005 (Box 11)
  - Google, 2004 (Box 11)
  - Hardt, Michael, 2001 (Box 11)
  - Harpham, Geoffrey, 2003-2004 (Box 11)
  - Heaton, Kelley, 2001-2002 (Box 11)
  - Harvard: Contact lists, 2004 (Box 11)
  - History: Mazundar, Sucheta, 2000 (Box 11)
  - History: French, John, 2001 (Box 11)
  - History of Philosophy of Science, 2004 (Box 11)
  - Holberg Prize: Fred Jameson, 2005 (Box 11)
  - Holland, Sharon, 2005 (Box 11)
  - Hong, Grace, 2006 (Box 11)
  - Human development undergraduate program, 2000-2002 (Box 11)
  - Imagining America consortium, 2003-2004 (Box 11)
  - FOCUS committee for ISIS, 2005 (Box 11)
  - ISIS (12 folders), 2001-2005 (Box 11)
  - Information technology resources, 1998-2000 (Box 11)
  - Inner staff, 2004-2006 (Box 11)
  - Innovative humanities course, 2005 (Box 11)
  - Institutional Equity, Office of, 1999-2005 (Box 11)
  - Insitutional Equity and Equal Employment Opportunity, 1999 (Box 11)
  - Institute of the Arts (Box 11)
  - Institute for Critical US Studies, 2004 (Box 11)
  - Institutes and university professorships, 1999-2004 (Box 11)
  - Instructional technology, 2001 (Box 11)
  - Interdisciplinary administrators, 2003-2005 (Box 11)
  - Interdisciplinary matrix structures, 2003 (Box 11)
  - Interdisciplinary faculty memo, 2005 (Box 11)
  - International Dunhang project, 1999-2002 (Box 11)
  - iPod, 2004 (Box 11)
  - Jakubs, Deborah, 2005 (Box 11)
  - Jenkins, Kim, 2005 (Box 11)
  - ISIS review responses (Box 12)
  - ISIS self evaluation; 5 year review (Box 12)
  - Common Fund proposals (Box 12)
  - ISIS general (Box 12)
  - Duke University Museum of Art Friends (Box 12)
  - Flyers (Box 12)
  - Analysis of trends and cumulative funding data (Box 12)
  - General information (Box 12)
  - Jenkins Professorship (Box 13)
  - Joint appointments, 2000 (Box 13)
  - Kaan, Edith, 2003 (Box 13)
  - Pogue, Zachary, Jenkins Lab analyst, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Academic Affairs Committee, University Professorships, 2002 (Box 13)
  - Balsamo, Anne, 2003 (Box 13)
  - Institution history: nominees, chairs deans, past committee members, 2003 (Box 13)
  - Jenkins chair website, 1999-2003 (Box 13)
  - MCAR, 2004 (Box 13)
  - National Humanities Center, 2001-2003 (Box 13)
  - Triangle Humanities Initiative, 1998-1999 (Box 13)
  - Taylor, Barbara, 2001 (Box 13)
  - National Science Foundation, 2001 (Box 13)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities Challenge Grant, 2002 (Box 13)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1998-2002 (Box 13)
  - National Academy of Science, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Muslim Network, 2003 (Box 13)
  - Luce Foundation, 2001-2002 (Box 13)
  - Luce Professorship, 2000-2001 (Box 13)
  - Lyman Award, 2003 (Box 13)
  - Managing at Duke, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Markets and Management studies, 2000 (Box 13)
  - McLendon, George, 2003 (Box 13)
  - MFA, 2003 (Box 13)
  - Merkx, Gil, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Miller, Lauren, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Mignolo, Walter, 2006 (Box 13)
  - Mitchell, Jess, 2003 (Box 13)
  - Moreiras, Alberto, 2003 (Box 13)
  - Moss, Jane, 2003 (Box 13)
  - Kang, Lin, 2003 (Box 13)
  - Review Committee for Kenan Institute, 2002-2003 (Box 13)
  - Kirk, Robin, 2003 (Box 13)
  - Latino Studies, 2005 (Box 13)
  - Law School: James Boyle, 2000-2001 (Box 13)
  - Lee, Celeste, 2006 (Box 13)
  - Lentricchia, Frank, 2003 (Box 13)
  - Lefcourt, Ellen, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Linguistics, 1999 (Box 13)
  - Literature program, 2000-2001 (Box 13)
  - NSF Grant Proposal: Library/ISIS/CSMN (Box 14)
  - Nepantla: Views from South (Box 14)
  - New Beginnings program (Box 14)
  - New Faculty orientation (Box 14)
  - New Markets, New Technologies (Box 14)
  - New Technologies, New Knowledges (Box 14)
  - NC Writers Conference (Box 14)
  - Patterson, Jane: E-NC Authority (Box 14)
  - Payne, Charles (Box 14)
  - Pedagogy Group (Box 14)
  - Philosophy of Biology, Center for (Box 14)
  - Physics, Dept. of (Box 14)
  - Keohane, Bob: political science (Box 14)
  - Program II (Box 14)
  - Provost's office (Box 14)
  - Provost's initiative in the arts (Box 14)
  - Public affairs (Box 14)
  - Public Domain, Center for (Box 14)
  - Public Policy Institute (Box 14)
  - Publishing subvention, Duke ACLS plan (Box 14)
  - Rabinhorst, Jim (Box 14)
  - Religion and the Arts: Luce Foundation (3 folders) (Box 14)
  - Renda, Molly (Box 14)
  - Riddell, Richard (Box 14)
  - Robertson Scholars (Box 14)
  - Rockefeller Foundation (2 folders) (Box 14)
  - Science and technology studies (Box 14)
  - Scholars at risk (Box 14)
  - SAS (Box 14)
  - Sease, Tony (Box 14)
  - Sexuality Studies, Program for (Box 14)
  - Shannon, Lawrie (Box 14)
  - Shepherd, Blair (Box 14)
  - Sippola-Thiele, Maria (Box 14)
  - Sister cities of Durham (Box 14)
  - Sitkin, Sim (Box 14)
  - Slavic and Eurasian studies (Box 14)
  - Smart boards (Box 14)
  - Smith, Brian Cantwell (Box 14)
  - Smith Fund (Box 14)
  - Sociology Dept. (Box 14)
  - Sommer, Doris (Box 14)
  - Sontag, David (Box 14)
  - Sports psychology (Box 14)
  - SSRI (Box 14)
  - Stanford (Box 14)
  - Starn, Orin (Box 14)
  - Stiles, Kristine (Box 14)
  - Student Affairs: Susan Coon (Box 14)
  - Student Affairs: Larry Moneta (Box 14)
  - Sugarman, Jeremy (Box 14)
  - Templeton Foundation (Box 14)
  - Thompson, John (Box 15)
  - Third Reconstruction Institute (Box 15)
  - Torgornick, Marianne (Box 15)
  - Triangle Center on Terrorism and Homeland Security (Box 15)
  - United States and South Africa, Center for (Box 15)
  - University Policies (18 folders) (Box 15)
  - University professors (Box 15)
  - USC (Box 15)
  - Van Ausdale, Debra (Box 15)
  - Vanderenne, Rick (Box 15)
  - Vertical integration (Box 15)
  - Wallace, Maurice (Box 15)
  - Warehouse (Box 15)
  - Whitton, Mary (Box 15)
  - Willard, Hunter (Box 15)
  - Women's Studies (Box 15)
  - Woodrow Wilson Foundation (Box 15)
  - Ybarra, Gary (Box 15)
  - Zakim, Eric (Box 15)
  - Common Fund, 1998-2001 (Box 15)
  - John Hope Franklin Center (JHFC) (Box 16)
    - General Information, 2003-2005 (Box 16)
    - Voucher Project, 2005 Asessment, 2004-2005 (Box 16)
    - Renovations, 2005 (Box 16)
    - Data Analysis, 2004-2005 (Box 16)
    - 2005-2006 Budget, Cost Analysis, 2004-2006 (Box 16)
    - Technology Within the Center, 2003-2004 (Box 16)
    - Budget, 2004-2005 (Box 16)
    - Budget Meeting, January 12, 2004 (Box 16)
    - Budget Meeting, March 5, 2003 (Box 16)
    - Franklin Center Review and Technology Audit, 2003 (Box 16)
    - Franklin Center Space Meeting, April 14, 2003 (Box 16)
    - Artist in Residence, Wendy Ewald, 2001-2002 (Box 16)
    - Brochure, 2001 (Box 16)
    - IT (Information Technology) Agreements, July 2004 (Box 16)
    - Organization Chart, undated (Box 16)
    - Position Descriptions, 2000 (Box 16)
    - Tech Interns (Box 16)
    - Meeting with Directors, April 16, 2002 (Box 16)
    - Grant Possibilities, 2000-2001 (Box 16)
    - Fundraising, 2001-2003 (Box 16)
    - Rob Sikorski, 2001-2002 (Box 16)
    - Transformations of Hanes Annex, 2000 (Box 16)
    - Franklin Center Development (Box 16)
      - Arts and Sciences, 2000-2001 (Box 16)
      - Correspondence with Foundations, 2001-2003 (Box 16)
      - Grant Possibilities, 2000-2001 (Box 16)
      - Davidson Trip to New York, May 2001 (Box 16)
      - Spring 1999-Summer 2000 (Box 16)
      - Stan Tanger, 2000-2001 (Box 16)
    - Fundraising Foundations, 2000 (Box 16)
    - Presidential Message, 2000-2001 (Box 16)
    - John Hope Franklin, 2003 (Box 16)
- 2009 Addition [UA2009-0037], (4 boxes) (Box 16)
  Includes personal and professional files of Cathy Davidson, Vice Provost of Interdisciplinary Studies. Includes materials on grant applications and proposals, including Rockefeller Foundation materials, Mellon grants, the LUCE proposal, and the Ford Foundation. Also includes files regarding Board of Trustees meetings, the Academic Council, Academic Affairs, the John Hope Franklin Center, various humanities centers and conferences, and information on English Dept. recruitment, candidates, and hiring.
  - UA2009-0037 (Box 17-20)
Related Material
Women's Studies Records.
University Archives, Duke University.